{
    "subject": "resource/The_Formula_(1980_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Marthe_Keller",
    "human_readable": "The film 'The Formula' stars Marthe Keller.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8671267628669739,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Marthe Keller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026110529899597,
            "question": "Name a movie that features Marthe Keller."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7716060280799866,
            "question": "Has Marthe Keller appeared in other films besides 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464715242385864,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228963136672974,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.557681679725647,
            "question": "Is Marthe Keller an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.373068243265152,
            "question": "When was the film 'The Formula' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3484461009502411,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3314206898212433,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Formula' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16508838534355164,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'The Formula'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'The Formula' stars Marthe Keller.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7965_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'The Formula' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7965_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'The Formula'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7965_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'The Formula' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7965_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7965_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because, according to the documents provided, there are multiple mentions of the film \"The Formula\" starring Marthe Keller. Therefore, the triple statement that The film 'The Formula' stars Marthe Keller is correct and supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7965/re-ranker-msmarco/27.txt` mentions Marthe Keller's role in the film 'The Formula' (1980), which supports the statement that the film 'The Formula' stars Marthe Keller."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}